Whitney Hung

whitneyhung.hello@gmail.com | 07407113416 | LinkedIn | Github | Website

PROFILE

Passionate for Data Visualization and Data Analysis with various experiences in Data Analysis on Psychology Research and Market Research, keen to details and reasoning.

Designs visualization graphs from users' perspectives.

Self-taught and specialises in analytic as well as web technologies, including R and Javascript.

Expected to graduate with MSc Psychology in summer 2019 with a focus on attention and information processing.

In search for a company to showcase my passion for data visualization.

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant, Modeling and Informatics Lab, Department of Psychology, National Taiwan University - Taiwan

Jan 2017 - June 2018

- Built interactive website (Javascript/HTML/CSS/PHP) for learning and memory experiment and data collection. Used Python to analyze frequency of wordings.
- Designed and conducted cognitive experiments of social cognition in learning and memory. Conducted Meta-Analysis research with R. Created charts with ggPlot2 to communicate the study. Research is published as conference paper, and submitted for journal.
- Recruited 5 college students to code word data into analytical data. Recruited and conducted experiments on 140 participants within three months.

Database Administrator,

March 2017 - June 2018

Standard Stimuli and Normative Responses of Emotions - Taiwan

- Checked 50 applicants' form and facilitated communication between database authors and applicants.
- Built a new website for the Taiwanese Psychological Association (TPA) and maintained the website.

Market Researcher, IPSOS - Taiwan

June 2015 – April 2016

- Designed, conducted and analyzed research studies on different industries including transportation, governmental studies, FMCG and cosmetic industries. Interpreted research findings to clients.
- Delivered findings to Japanese co-workers for the Japanese counterpart client company.
- Adopted business models to process research. Used Data Visualisation to communicate findings to clients.

PUBLICATION

Hung, W., Ng, K.T., & Huang, T.-R. (2018) Retrieval-Induced Forgetting in Social Contexts: A Meta-Analysis. The 30th Association for Psychological Science (APS) Convention. San Francisco, USA.

EDUCATION

Goldsmiths, University of London - London, UK

Sept 2018 - Present

MSc in Psychology of the Arts, Neuroaesthetics and Creativity, Department of Psychology

- Modules: Aesthetic Science, Creativity, Multivariate Statistical Models, Foundations of Neuroscience, Creative Coding
- Audit: Digital Sandbox

Uppsala University - Sweden

Sept 2012 - June 2013

One-year exchange study, Department of Business Studies

- Modules: International Business, Consumer Behaviour, International Marketing
- Awards:

The Best Project Performance: Group project with four Swedish teammates in The International Business Course Project Competition, project name: Geely's Against on of Volvo.

National Chengchi University - Taiwan

Sept 2009 - Jan 2014

B.A. Department of Diplomacy, College of International Affairs

- Modules: International Relations, Quantitative Social Science Statistical Analysis
- GPA: 3.7/4
- Awards:

Best Delegation, Taipei Model United Nations
The Academic Acheivement Award (Top 5%), Department of Korean Language and Culture

SKILLS

Technical R | Javascript | Python | HTML/CSS | Openframeworks | Adobe Illustrator | PHP | SPSS Languages Mandarin Chinese (Native), English (Fluent), Korean(Conversational), Swedish(Basic)

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCES

Secretary, Taiwanese Psychological Association

Jan 2017 - June 2018

• Standardised administrative work for the association. Worked in a team to organise the 56th Annual Taiwanese Psychological Conference.

Internship, Political and Economic Section, American Institute in Taiwan

Mar - June 2012

• Facilitated biography profiles of Taiwanese politicians. Refined translation skills of professional Chinese and English.

OTHER INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES

Violin, learning languages and jogging

President, Taiwanese Community, Goldsmiths University, London UK

Finished 2018 PUMA Night run Half Marathon, Taipei Taiwan

Finished 2014 NIKE Women Half Marathon, Taipei Taiwan

Volunteer, Marketing Sector, 32nd Uppsala International Short Film Festival 2013, Uppsala Sweden

OTHER INFORMATION

Tier 4 Visa

References available upon request